$ocum_header_main_settings	Main OCum Settings
$ocum_header_adjustments	Adjustments
$ocum_header_reset	Reset Options
$ocum_option_clean_water_enter	Clean cum when character enters water
$ocum_option_disable_cum_shots	Disable cum shots
$ocum_option_disable_cum_decals	Disable cum decals
$ocum_option_disable_cum_inflation	Disable cum inflation
$ocum_option_cum_regen_speed	Cum Regeneration Speed
$ocum_option_squirt_chance	Squirt chance
$ocum_option_cum_cleanup_timer	Cum cleanup time (in real life minutes)
$ocum_option_inflation_cleanup_timer	Inflation cleanup time (in real life minutes)
$ocum_option_cum_bar_key	Show cum bar key
$ocum_option_realistic_cum_mode	Enable realistic cum application mode
$ocum_option_clean_cum_decals	Clean cum decals from all actors
$ocum_option_clear_inflation	Clear inflation from all actors
$ocum_option_reset_defaults	Reset all options to defaults
$ocum_message_box_option_yes	Yes
$ocum_message_box_option_no	No
$ocum_highlight_clean_water_enter	Sets whether cum textures are cleaned when characters enter water. Note that when you change this option, it only takes effect on cummed characters after the option is changed. Characters that already have cum in them will not be affected, unless they are cummed on again.
$ocum_highlight_disable_cum_shots	Enable or disable cumshots. These are the projectiles that come out of the schlong on orgasm. Does not affect cum texture application.
$ocum_highlight_disable_cum_decals	Enable or disable cum decals. These are the textures that are applied to the body, face, feet and hands on orgasm.
$ocum_highlight_disable_cum_inflation	Enable or disable cum inflation. This is the belly inflation that occurs after a female actor is overfilled with cum. Note that you need HUGE amounts of cum for this effect to apply. Usually only possible with very high level characters.
$ocum_highlight_cum_regen_speed	Set how fast cum regenerates for male characters. This is a multiplier value between 0.1 and 2. If it is set to 2, it means it regenerates twice as fast as default.
$ocum_highlight_squirt_chance	Sets the probability of female squirting on orgasm. 100 means she will always squirt on every orgasm.
$ocum_highlight_cum_cleanup_timer	Set how long it takes for cum textures to disappear from characters who have cum on them. This value is in real life minutes. Note that when you change this option, it only takes effect on characters that are cummed on after the option is changed.
$ocum_highlight_inflation_cleanup_timer	Set how long it takes for cum inflation to be cleared from characters whose belly is inflated or starting to be inflated by cum. This value is in real life minutes. Note that when you change this option, it only takes effect on characters that are inflated after the option is changed.
$ocum_highlight_cum_bar_key	Set which key displays the cum bar.
$ocum_highlight_realistic_cum_mode	Enabling this option will apply only reasonable or more realistic amounts of cum, independent of character level. For instance, if you cum inside the vagina, cum textures might not be applied on the body. Enable this if you think the cum application is too excessive.
$ocum_highlight_clean_cum_decals	Click this option to clean cum textures from all characters who currently have applied. For emergency in case cum doesn't clean off by normal means, or if you simply want to reset cum textures which were applied.
$ocum_highlight_clear_inflation	Click this option to clear inflation from all characters who currently have inflation (even if the effect is not yet noticeable). For emergency in case belly inflation isn't removed by normal means, or if you simply want to remove belly inflation from characters who currently have it.
$ocum_message_cum_cleaned	Cum decals have been cleaned from all actors.
$ocum_message_inflation_cleaned	Cum inflation has been cleared from all actors.
$ocum_message_defaults_reset	All options have been reset to their defaults.
