$ocum_header_main_settings	Main OCum Settings
$ocum_header_adjustments	Adjustments
$ocum_header_reset	Reset Options
$ocum_option_clean_water_enter	Clean cum when character enters water
$ocum_option_disable_cum_shots	Disable cum shots
$ocum_option_disable_cum_decals	Disable cum decals
$ocum_option_disable_cum_meshes	Disable cum meshes
$ocum_option_disable_facials_elins	Disable facials for Tera Elin race actors
$ocum_option_cum_regen_speed	Cum Regeneration Speed
$ocum_option_squirt_chance	Squirt chance
$ocum_option_creampie_chance	Creampie chance
$ocum_option_analpie_chance	Analpie chance
$ocum_option_cum_cleanup_timer	Cum cleanup time (in real life minutes)
$ocum_option_cum_bar_key	Show cum bar key
$ocum_option_clean_cum_decals	Clean cum decals from all actors
$ocum_option_reset_actor	Reset this actor:
$ocum_option_reset_defaults	Reset all options to defaults
$ocum_option_enable_higher_cum_regen_speed	Enable higher cum regen speed
$ocum_option_cum_bar_max_amount_npcs	Male NPC max cum storage
$ocum_option_cum_bar_max_amount_player	Male player character max cum storage
$ocum_message_box_option_yes	Yes
$ocum_message_box_option_no	No
$ocum_highlight_clean_water_enter	Sets whether cum textures are cleaned when characters enter water. Note that when you change this option, it only takes effect on cummed characters after the option is changed. Characters that already have cum in them will not be affected, unless they are cummed on again.
$ocum_highlight_disable_cum_shots	Enable or disable cumshots. These are the projectiles that come out of the schlong on orgasm. Does not affect cum texture application.
$ocum_highlight_disable_cum_decals	Enable or disable cum decals. These are the textures that are applied to the body, face, feet and hands on orgasm.
$ocum_highlight_disable_cum_meshes	Enable or disable cum meshes. Cum meshes are 3D cum effects used for creampie and analpie. Cum meshes do NOT stay on after OStim scenes end, as they are an equippable item like an armour.
$ocum_highlight_cum_regen_speed	Set how fast cum regenerates for male characters. This is a multiplier value between 0.1 and 2. If it is set to 2, it means it regenerates twice as fast as default.
$ocum_highlight_squirt_chance	Sets the probability of female squirting on orgasm. 100 means she will always squirt on every orgasm.
$ocum_highlight_cum_cleanup_timer	Set how long it takes for cum textures to disappear from characters who have cum on them. This value is in real life minutes. Note that when you change this option, it only takes effect on characters that are cummed on after the option is changed.
$ocum_highlight_cum_bar_key	Set which key displays the cum bar. Set to Esc to disable it.
$ocum_highlight_clean_cum_decals	Click this option to clean cum textures from all characters who currently have applied. For emergency in case cum doesn't clean off by normal means, or if you simply want to reset cum textures which were applied.
$ocum_highlight_disable_facials_elins	Sets whether facial cum textures will be disabled for Tera Elin actors or not. Tera Elin race uses different head maps than the normal races, so the facial textures may not look good. Enable this option if you don't like the facials on Elin characters.
$ocum_highlight_enable_higher_cum_regen_speed	Enable this option to be able to select higher cum regen speeds in the cum regen slider below (up to 50x)
$ocum_highlight_cumbar_max_amount	Set max cum storage.
$ocum_highlight_reset_actor	Completely reset the actor in the crosshair. To reset the Player character, simply have nothing in your crosshair. This will clean cum decals, cum meshes, and reset the cum bar for the actor if it is broken.
$ocum_highlight_creampie_chance	Set the chance for a creampie to occur when orgams on vaginal intercourse occur. This will do nothing if cum meshes are disabled.
$ocum_highlight_analpie_chance	Set the chance for an analpie to occur when orgams on anal intercourse occur. This will do nothing if cum meshes are disabled.
$ocum_message_cum_cleaned	Cum decals have been cleaned from all actors.
$ocum_message_defaults_reset	All options have been reset to their defaults.
$ocum_message_cum_meshes_warning	You have enabled cum meshes. THEY BREAK OAHEGAO IF YOU ARE PLAYING A FEMALE CHARACTER, AND ALSO RESET FACIAL EXPRESSIONS WHEN THE CUM MESHES ARE APPLIED! If you use any version of OAhegao, please disable cum meshes! Ignore this warning if you don't use OAhegao or if you play a Male character.
$ocum_message_reset_actor	Actor has been reset.
